A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Political Files, Series 24 FA367
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1959-1960, 1; 19 Cubic Feet
  - New York State Correspondence (Ga), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 529)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ge), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 530)
  - New York State Correspondence (Gi), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 531)
  - New York State Correspondence (Go), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 532)
  - New York State Correspondence (Gu), 1960 (Box 12, Folder 533)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ha), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 534)
  - New York State Correspondence (He), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 535)
  - New York State Correspondence (Hi), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 536)
  - New York State Correspondence (Ho), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 537)
  - New York State Correspondence (Hu), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 538)
  - New York State Correspondence (I), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 539)
  - New York State Correspondence (J), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 540)
  - New York State Correspondence (K), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 541)
  - New York State Correspondence (Wo), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 542)
  - New York State Correspondence (X), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 543)
  - New York State Correspondence (Y), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 544)
  - New York State Correspondence (Z), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 545)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ai), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 546)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Am), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 547)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (As), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 548)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Av), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 549)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ba), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 550)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Be), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 551)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Bi), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 552)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Bo), 1960; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 553)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Bo), 1960; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 554)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Br), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 555)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Bro), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 556)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Bu), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 557)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (By), 1960 (Box 13, Folder 558)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1960; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 13, Folder 559)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (C), 1960; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 14, Folder 560)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ce), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 561)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ci), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 562)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Co), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 563)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Com), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 564)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Cr), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 565)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (D), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 566)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (De), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 567)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Di), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 568)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Do), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 569)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Du), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 570)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (E), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 571)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (F), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 572)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ge), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 573)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (H), 1960 (Box 14, Folder 574)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Har), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 575)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (He), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 576)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Hi), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 577)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ho), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Hoy), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Hu), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (I), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (J), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Je), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 583)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Jo), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 584)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ju), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 585)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (K), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 586)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ke), 1960 (Box 15, Folder 587)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ki), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ko), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ku), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1960; Folder 1 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (L), 1960; Folder 2 of 2 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Le), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Lo), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (M), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Mc), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Me), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (N), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 598)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (O), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 599)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Po), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 600)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (R), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 601)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ri), 1960 (Box 16, Folder 602)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Ru), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 603)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (S), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 604)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Sch), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 605)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Sh), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 606)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Si), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 607)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Sm), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 608)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (So), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 609)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Tuy), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 610)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (V), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 611)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (W), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 612)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (We), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 613)
  - New York State and Political Correspondence - No Answer (Wh), 1960 (Box 17, Folder 614)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Westchester County Dinner, January 22, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 615)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Republican Victory Dinner, January 28, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 616)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Empire State Chamber of Commerce Meeting, February 3, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 617)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Lincoln Day Dinner, February 12, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 618)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - "Milk for Health Breakfast", February 17, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 619)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - The American Jewish Congress Luncheon, February 18, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 620)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Radio and TV Broadcasters Association, March 3, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 621)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Civil Service Employees Dinner, March 4, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 622)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York Board of Rabbis Speech, March 6, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 623)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Legislative Correspondents Dinner, March 14, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 624)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Citizens Council on Traffic Safety, March 31, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 625)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Ceremonies Opening the Italian Institute of Culture, April 6, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 626)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Lotos Club Dinner, April 14, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 627)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Boy Scout Exposition, April 14, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 628)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Long Island Home Builders, April 18, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 629)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dedication of Two Dormitories at State University, April 30, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 630)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Main Street Association, April 30, 1959 (Box 17, Folder 631)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Erie County Republican Committee, April 30, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 632)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dedication at Corning, April 30, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 633)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Loyalty Day Parade, May 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 634)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Polish-American Congress, May 3, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 635)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Essay Contest, May 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 636)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Plattsburgh State College, May 6, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 637)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Thruway Ceremony, May 26, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 638)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Citizen's Union Annual Searchlight Dinner, May 27, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 639)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Bronxville Republican Women's Club, May 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 640)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Westchester County Association, May 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 641)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Finger Lakes Association, June 1, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 642)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Hooker Chemical Corporation, June 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 643)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Republican State Committee Dinner, June 4, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 644)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State Association of Real Estate Boards - Lake George, June 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 645)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Rotary Convention, June 9, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 646)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York Conference of Mayors, June 9, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 647)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Hudson-Champlain Ceremony, June 10, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 648)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Hudson Celebration, June 11, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 649)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Van Cortlandt Manor Restoration, June 13, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 650)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Civil Defense Warning System, June 17, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 651)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Long Beach Republican Dinner, June 18, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 652)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State District Attorney's Association, June 20, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 653)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Society of Newspaper Editors, June 22, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 654)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Supervisors Association, June 23, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 655)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Israel Bond Dinner, June 24, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 656)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State Citizens Council Institute, June 25, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 657)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Time Editors Luncheon, June 26, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 658)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - St. Lawrence Seaway and Power Plant, June 27, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 659)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Task Force Meeting on Fallout Protection, June 29, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 660)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Lions Club, June 30, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 661)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Meeting of Bank Presidents, July 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 662)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Rotary Club Luncheon, July 7, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 663)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - North East Kiwanis Club - Rochester, July 7, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 664)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) Convention, July 13, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 665)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Republican Committee Dinner - Watertown, July 18, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 666)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Camp Drum Review - Watertown, July 18, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 667)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Opening of Caribbean Trade Development Office, August 6, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 668)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - National Association of State Budget Officers, August 19, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 669)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Jones Beach State Park, August 20, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 670)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Meeting State Fair Finalists, August 27, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 671)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Meeting - National Students Traffic Safety Association, September 3, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 672)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - World's Fair Group, September 4, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 673)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Farm Dinner - Syracuse, September 9, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 674)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State Fair - Syracuse, September 10, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 675)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Eisenhower Fellowship Dinner, September 14, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 676)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Opening of New Industry - Amsterdam, September 17, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 677)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Khrushchev Visit, September 18, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 678)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dedication of Temple Congregation Shaaray Tefila, September 20, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 679)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Mortgage Banks Association, September 21, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 680)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Circus Saints and Sinners, September 22, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 681)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Joint Defense Appeal, September 22, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 682)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Meeting of Mortgage Bankers Association, September 23, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 683)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Long Island Press Dinner, September 24, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 684)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Fire Prevention Conference, September 24, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 685)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Associated Industries Meeting, September 24, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 686)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - University Hospital Founder's Day, September 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 687)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - County Officers Association - Grossingers, September 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 688)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Civil Defense Directors Meeting, September 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 689)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - International Association of Chiefs of Police, September 28, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 690)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Federation of Jewish Philanthropies, September 29, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 691)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Magazine Publishers Association Fall Conference Luncheon, September 29, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 692)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - National Fund for Medical Education, September 29, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 693)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Magazine Publishers Association, September 29, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 694)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Family Fund - Campaign of Community Service Society, September 30, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 695)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Northway Tape, October 1, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 696)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Visit to Camp Pharsalia, October 2, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 697)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Banquet for General Pulaski Memorial Committee, October 4, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 698)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dinner in Honor of Prime Minister Segni of Italy, October 4, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 699)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - White House Conference on Children and Youth, October 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 700)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Board of Trade Gold Award Dinner, October 8, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 701)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Albany Community Chest Meeting, October 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 702)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Opening of Court of Appeals Building, October 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 703)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dinner in Honor of Prime Minister Segni of Italy, October 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 704)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - General Electric Managers Meeting, October 5, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 705)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Radio Script for John D. Bennett's Election, October 7, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 706)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Regional Plan Conference, October 7, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 707)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - International Basic Economy Corporation (IBEC) Group Meeting, October 8, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 708)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Employ the Physically Handicapped, October 9, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 709)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Columbus Day Dinner of Columbus Citizens Committee, October 12, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 710)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Girl Scout Council of Greater New York, October 14, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 711)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Order of Eastern Star, October 14, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 712)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Investment Bankers of America, October 14, 1959 (Box 18, Folder 713)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - 87th Annual Meeting - Public Health Association, October 19, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 714)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Speech Drafts for Inland Press Association, October 20, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 715)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Inland Daily Press Association, October 20, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 716)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Young Womens Christian Association (YWCA) Annual Luncheon, October 20, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 717)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State Congress of Parents and Teachers, October 21, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 718)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Alfred E. Smith Memorial Dinner, October 22, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 719)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Society of Foreign Consuls Luncheon, October 22, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 720)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - World's Fair Committee - Washington, October 23, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 721)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Cayuga City Republican Committee, October 26, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 722)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dedication of the New Research Building, October 26, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 723)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State Boards Association, October 26, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 724)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Opening of Section of Adirondack Northway, October 27, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 725)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dedication of State Police Troop "G" Headquarters, October 27, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 726)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Governor's Council on Rehabilitation, October 29, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 727)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Emmanuel Baptist Church, October 29, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 728)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Dr. Thomas Hale Hamilton - Installation Ceremonies, October 29, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 729)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Tappan Hill Dinner, October 30, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 730)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Westchester Tour, October 31, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 731)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Wind-up Dinner of Republican Committee at Eastchester, October 31, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 732)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Eastchester Town Republican Committee Dinner, October 31, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 733)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Labor Dinner in New York City, November 4, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 734)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Protestant Welfare Agencies, November 5, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 735)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Economic Club of New York, November 9, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 736)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - United Neighborhood Houses Luncheon, November 9, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 737)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - National Conference of Christians and Jews, November 11, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 738)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - World Affairs Council, November 12, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 739)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Western States Republican Committee, November 12, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 740)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Young Republican Cocktail Party - San Francisco, November 13, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 741)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Press and Union Club, November 13, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 742)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Convocation at Willamette University, Novemer 14, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 743)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New York State American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO) Convention, November 16, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 744)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Annual Freedom Award Dinner, November 16, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 745)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - National Foreign Trade Council World Trade Dinner, November 18, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 746)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - New England Society of Newspaper Editors Dinner, November 19, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 747)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Martin B. McKneally Dinner, November 19, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 748)
  - Dinners and Luncheons - Women's National Republican Club, November 19, 1959 (Box 19, Folder 749)
- 1961-1962, 2; 12 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of both answered and unanswered letters to Governor Rockefeller and responses from 1961 and 1962. The New York State Republican Matters folders, the Out of State Republican Matters folders, and the County Briefing Notes from 1962 are unique to this subseries.
  - Miscellaneous Research Papers, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 750)
  - Miscellaneous Research Papers, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 19, Folder 751)
  - Miscellaneous Reports and Articles (Box 19, Folder 752)
  - Letters to L. Judson Morhouse (Box 19, Folder 753)
  - Letters from L. Judson Morhouse (Box 19, Folder 754)
  - L. Judson Morhouse - Memos - National Politics (Box 19, Folder 755)
  - L. Judson Morhouse - Memos - Peace Corps (Box 19, Folder 756)
  - Rogalin, Wilma (Box 19, Folder 757)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - New York State Politics (Box 19, Folder 758)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen Matters (Box 19, Folder 759)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - Newspaper and TV Matters (Box 19, Folder 760)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - Republican Yearbooks (Box 19, Folder 761)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - State Legislation (Box 19, Folder 762)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - Appointments (Box 19, Folder 763)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - Progress/Project Report (Box 20, Folder 764)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Memos - New York City Politics (Box 20, Folder 765)
  - New York State Republican Matters - People, Polls, and Politics (Box 20, Folder 766)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Republican Calendar of Events (Box 20, Folder 767)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Campaign Projects - Hugh Morrow (Box 20, Folder 768)
  - New York State Republican Matters - 1962 State Convention Material (Box 20, Folder 769)
  - New York State Republican Matters - MORE (Mobilization of Republican Enterprise) (Box 20, Folder 770)
  - New York State Republican Matters - List of Upstate New York Finance Committee (Box 20, Folder 771)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Happiness Index (Box 20, Folder 772)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Vote Tally in New York State (Box 20, Folder 773)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Congressional Re-Districting (Box 20, Folder 774)
  - New York State Republican Matters - State Committee Finance Statements (Box 20, Folder 775)
  - New York State Republican Matters - Republican County Committees (Box 20, Folder 776)
  - New York State Republican Matters - New York County Republican Planning Committee (Box 20, Folder 777)